Guide to the Organization of Staff Analysts Records WAG.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Agencies
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Metropolitan Hospital Center, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Morrisania Neighborhood Family Care Center, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Morrisania Neighborhood Family Care Center, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Nurse Referral, Inc., 1993 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Queens Hospital Center, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Queens Hospital Center, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Renaissance Health Care Network, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Renaissance Health Care Network, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Seaview Hospital and Home, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Segundo Ruiz Belvis Diagnostic and Treatment Center (D & TC), 1993 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Woodhull Medical and Mental Health Center, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Woodhull Medical and Mental Health Center, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Memorandum of Understanding (Layoffs); Executed Copy, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): 1998 Severance IV Memorandum of Agreement (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): North Central Analysts Lists, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Bellevue Hospital Center, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Bronx Municipal Hospital Center, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Central Office, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Coler Memorial Hospital, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Coney Island hospital, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Cumberland Diagnostic and Treatment Center, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - East New York NFCC, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Elmhurst Hospital, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Emergency Medical Services, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Goldwater Memorial Hospital, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Gouverneur Hospital, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Harlem Hospital Center, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Kings County Hospital Center, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Lincoln Medical and Mental Health Center, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Med-Plan, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Metropolitan Hospital Center, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Morrisania Diagnostic and Treatment Center, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Neponsit HCC, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Queens Hospital Center, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Renaissance Diagnostic and Treatment Center, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Sea View Hospital and Home, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Organizing Drive - Woodhull Hospital, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Personnel Rules and Regulations, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Bellevue Hospital Center "A-H", 1993 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Bellevue Hospital Center "J-P", 1993 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Bellevue Hospital Center "R-Z", 1993 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Bronx Municipal Hospital Center (BMHC) "A-G", 1993 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Bronx Municipal Hospital Center (BMHC) "H-P", 1993 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Bronx Municipal Hosp. Center (BMHC) "R-W", 1993 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Central Office "A-F", 1993 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Central Office "G-P", 1993 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Central Office "R-Z", 1993 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Coler Memorial Hospital, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Coney Island Hospital "A-L", 1993 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Coney Island Hospital "M-Z", 1993 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Cumberland Diagnostic and Treatment Center (D & TC), 1993 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - East New York Diagnostic and Treatment Center (D & TC), 1993 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Elmhurst Hospital, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Emergency Medical Services (EMS), 1993 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Goldwater Memorial Hospital, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Gouverneur Hospital, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Harlem Hospital, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Kings County Hospital "A-L", 1993 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Kings County Hospital "M-Z", 1993 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Lincoln Hospital, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Metropolitan Hospital Center "A-L", 1993 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Metropolitan Hospital Center "M-Z", 1993 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Morrisania Neighborhood Family Care Center, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Queens Hospital Center "A-M", 1993 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Queens Hospital Center "N-Z", 1993 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Renaissance Health Care Network, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Seaview Hospital and Home, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Segundo Ruiz Belvis Diagnostic and Treatment Center (D & TC), 1993 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Position Description Questionnaire - Woodhull Medical and Mental Health Center, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Reassignment, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Request for Proposals (RFP) for provision of comprehensive medical mental health, dental and ancillary services for inmates in the custody of the New York City Department of Corrections, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Summary of Employees (re: Training and Development Associate et al), May 19, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Supplemental Agreement (Executed) to Staff Analysts 1992-1995 Agreement, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Housing Authority: General, 1990s (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Housing Authority: General, 2000s (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Housing Authority: Insurance Advisor, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Housing Authority: Letter from Roy Sicular re: Bob Croghan, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Human Resources Administration (HRA): Audit of Family Homemaking and Family Housekeeping Cases, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Human Resources Administration (HRA): City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Human Resources Administration (HRA): Employee Disciplinary Manual (Draft), Feb 2, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Human Resources Administration (HRA): Employee Discipline Manual, undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Human Resources Administration (HRA): Managerial/Confidential (ZZ), 1992 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Law Department: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating Authority (MABOSTOA): General, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating Authority (MABOSTOA) Organizing Drive (same materials to TA), 1993 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - MTA (Metropolitan Transit Authority) New York City Transit: General, 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - New York City Housing Authority (NYCHA): Local 237 Collective Bargaining, Dec 10, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Office of Payroll Administration (OPA): City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Office of Personnel Services: Payroll Clerk Directory, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Police Department: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Police Department: Collective Bargaining Demands, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Police Department: Managerial/Confidential (ZZ), 1991-1992 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Probation Department: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Taxi and Limousine Commission: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Agreement between New York City TA and Civil Service Technical Guild, effective, Jul 1, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Agreement between New York City TA and District Council 37, effective, Jul 1, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Alphabetical [directory used for organizing], 1998 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Benefits Booklet, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Draft Agreement between TA and OSA, Feb 25, 1999-Jun 30, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Employee Benefits Program, Jul 2001 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Employee Lists, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Transit Authority (TA): General, 1990s-2000s (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Health Benefit Booklets, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Negotiations, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Transit Authority (TA): New Insurance Coverage, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Organizing of TA - lists, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Organizing of TA - written materials, 1987, 1991-1994 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Organizing of TA - written materials, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Organizing of TA - written materials and lists, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Rulebook Draft, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Transit Authority (TA): Temporary Flex Time/Lunch Time Stipulation, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Transit Authority (TA) and Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating Authority (MABOSTOA): General (on same material), 1990s (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Transit Supervisors Organization (TSO): Agency Shop Fees, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Transit Supervisors Organization (TSO): Organizing Drive, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Series IV: Unprocessed Materials, 1980-2005
  - Hearing on the "One-in-Three" Rule, May 4, 2004 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Board of Education - Municipal Coalition Agreement, 1991-1995 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Contracts - OSA Demands - Negotiations, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Court Cases - Board of Education vs. Public Employment Relations Board (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Contracts, 1985-1994 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Contracts - Muncipal Labor Coalition Agreement - Gain Sharing Proposals, 5/20/1993 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Contracts, 7/1988-9/30/1990 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Contracts - City Wide Agreement - Sick Leave for Family Illness - Article 5, Section 5, 1990-1992 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Contracts - City Wide Contract - Supper Money through Payroll Management System, 11/13/1990 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Contracts - City-Wide Agreement - Arbitration on Longevity, 1987-1990 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Contracts City-Wide - Contracts and Negotiations, 7/1/1990-6/30/1992 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Contracts - City Wide Contract Equity Panel, 1987-1990 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Contracts - City Wide Contracts, 1985-1987 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Contracts - City Wide Contract, 1980-1982 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - City Wide Contract, 7/1/1976-6/30/1978 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Contract MCMEA, MLC-MCMEA Transitional Funding Agreement, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Contracts MCMLA - MLC Negotiations, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Contracts - City Wide Control (Municipal Coalition Agreement) - One Time Lump Sum Payment of $700, 1992-1995 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Contract - City Wide Contract - Municipal Coalition Agreement (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Campaign for Analysts in Local 371 SSEU (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Campaign, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Campaign, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Certification of Titles, 5/19/1988 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Certification Presentation Proceedings - Analysts, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Certification - Hearings with PERB #C-2190 and #E-0176 - Improper Practice Stipulation, 7/19/1985 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Campaign, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Exams - Associate Supervisor of School Safety #9559, 1/2004 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Principal Administrative Associate Exam Preperation for Analysts, 3/2009 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Exam Day, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Appeals Staff Analyst, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Materials Staff Analyst, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Exams Staff Analyst #3045 Application Preperation - No College, 3/3/2004-3/23/2004 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Reference Booklet Staff Analyst (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Staff Analyst Exam Training, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Study Guide for the Staff Analyst Exam (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Associate Staff Analyst Prom - Legal Problem, 6/2001 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Exam Material (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Exam Material (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Associate Staff Analyst Preperation Training, 2/94, 5/94 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Tapes, Video - Associate Staff Analyst Training, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Associate Staff Analyst Trainer Awards, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Staff Analyst Etc., 1992 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - OMD Grievance (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Human Resources Admin - Office of Family Service Redeployment, 4/1991 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - HRA/OFS, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - HRA - OMD Transfer, 6/1990 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Welfare Fund Minutes (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Alcohol/Drugs/AIDs Program (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Contract with America (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Democratic Club (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Employee Benefits Program - Medical Spending Conversion (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - NYC Rules and Regulations, 3/31/1992 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - NYC Voter Assistance Commission, 11/12/1993 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Arthur's Group (Majority Coalition Platform) (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Blackout, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Administration for Children Services Media/Press Policy, 10/1/1999 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Award (Savings Bond Drive) (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Employee Recognition Awards (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Credit Card Agreement - Republic National Bank, 8/1996 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Campaign for Ferrer, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Deferred Wages (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Tional Emerald Society (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Board of Examiners, June 22, 1990; Sept 26, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - HRA - Construction 250 Church St., 1/1993 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - HRA - CWA Audit, 4/1991 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - HRA 109 E 16 St. Construction, 5/1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - HRA- Office of Facility Management (BRAR), 8/1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - HRA - Office of Employment Services, 3/1988 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - HRA - Office of Child Support Enforcement/SCU Procedure, 5/1991 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Awards Dinner, 10/28/1993 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Construction 110 Church St., 2/1993 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Administration for Children's Services Master of Social Work Program, 1/1998 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Tech Guild News (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Tax Reform - Arthur Cheliotes, 5/1991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Sabbaticals (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Satterwhite Training Academy (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Sabol, Barbara (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Fiscal Crisis, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Fernando Ferrer Bronx Boro President (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Training - Cornell University Grievance Training (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Taxi and Limousine Commission, 8/24/1994 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Voice Processing (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - US Senators (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Exams - ASA Promotional Lists of #2581, 2584, 2588, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Exams - ASA Promotional Lists, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Exams - Administrative Manager Promotional #8578, 10/19/1985 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Exams - ASA Promotional Notice of Exam, 7/21/1982 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Exams - ASA Promotional Appeal, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Exams - ASA Promotion - ASA Promotion Committee, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Exams - ASA Promotion - Request for City Wide List, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - ASA List #2584, 3/26/1997 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - ASA Promotional List #2581, 2584, 2588, March 1997 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - ASA Promotional List Exams #2581, 2584, 2588, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Exams - Staff Analyst - #2063 - Notice of Exam, 5/1983 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Exam - SA #2066 E & E Announcements, 5/1993 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Staff Analyst - E & E, 6/1993 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Exams - SA - E & E - #2066, 10/1992 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Exam #2063 - Eligible Lists Certification, 10/12/1984 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Health and Safety Committee - DCAS, 2001-2004 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Contract Specialist, 9/1994 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Enrollment Sales Representatives Offical Papers (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Mailings and Handouts (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Enrollment Sales Representative (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Welfare Fund Financial Reports (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Misc. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Worker's Compensation (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, December 31, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - 6.1.9. Requests, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Directive 12 - Comptroller's Guidelines - Letters to/from S. Hill, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Executive Order 75 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Deparment of Juvenile Justice - Operations Order, 6/21/2005 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Fund, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 5/2007 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Welfare Fund, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Welfare Fund, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Welfare Fund, 2004-2005 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Welfare Fund, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Welfare Fund, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Welfare Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Welfare Fund, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Fund, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Welfare Fund, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Welfare Fund, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Welfare Fund, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Fund, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Welfare Fund, 1997 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Welfare Fund, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Welfare Fund, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Welfare Fund, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Welfare Fund, June 1989 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Fund, 3/1989-5/1989 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Welfare Fund, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Benefits Fund, Up to 3/1/1989 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Group Insurance Statement and Financial Records, 3/1/1986-10/27/1989 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Welfare Fund - Guardians Life Insurance Info, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Welfare Fund - Legal Services Info, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Welfare Fund - Summary Plan Description, Local 272, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Welfare Fund Benefits - LTD W-2s, 12/1999 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Welfare Fund Benefits - District Council 37 (Full Time/Retirees), Undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - District Council 37 - Welfare Fund Reciprocal Agreement, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Retirees Retro Payment, 2001 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Questionnaire - OSA Duties, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Maxon Company, Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Healthplex, Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Dental Plans Negotiations - Vendors, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Dental Fee Increases (possible), 7/1995 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - LID-Union Proposal, 10/1995 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Mutual of Omaha Mony - STD Benefits (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Medical Expense - Welfare Fund, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - ASA List - Members Correspondence - Requests for Restoration and Complaints - Agency 806-998, 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - ASA Exam - Correspondence re: Department of Health and Mental Hygiene - Rule 5.4.2., 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - ASA List - DCAS vs. OSA - Material Exam - 0509, 2/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - NYC Housing Authority ASA Certification Case, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - NYC Housing Authority Case (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - ASA List - Members Correspondence - Requests for Restoration and Complaints - Agency - 02-801, 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Freedom of Information Law Correspondence - ASA List, 10/2001-10/2005 (Box 40, Folder 14)